The
lights are bright, but the room is cold. Another
story that's bored and sold. I'm trying to find a
reason why Beneath this plastic, empty sky
When the world is spinning out of my control
You're the one true thing that I can hold
Through the static and the driving rain You're
the one who keeps me sane You are the shelter They
pull us under, they push us high
They build us up just to watch us die It's hard to
know who you can trust When all the promises turn
to dust
But when the world is spinning out of my control
You're the one true thing that I can hold Through
the static and the driving rain You're the one
who keeps me sane You are the shelter You are the
truth, my anchor in this crazy you.
So let
them talk, let them stare As long as you are
standing there I'm not afraid of what's to come I
know where I belong
Cause when the world is spinning out of my
control You're the one true thing that I can hold
Through the static and the driving rain You're
the one who keeps me sane You are the shelter You
are the truth My anchor in this crazy you My
anchor My anchor holds
You are
the truth